export const generalKnowledge = [
	{
		question: 'Which planet in the solar system is known as the “Red Planet”?',
		options: ['Venus', 'Earth', 'Mars', 'Jupiter'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: ' What chemical element is designated as “Hg”?',
		options: ['Silver', 'Tin', 'Copper', 'Mercury'],
		correctOption: 3,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'What ocean lies between North America and Eurasia?',
		options: ['Quiet', 'Atlantic', 'Indian', 'Arctic'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question:
			' India is a federal union comprising twenty-eight states and how many union territories?',
		options: ['6', '7', '8', '9'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which city is known as the “summer capital” of Jammu and Kashmir?',
		options: ['Jammu', 'Srinagar', 'Shimla', 'Anantnag'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question:
			'If the actual unemployment rate is below the natural rate of unemployment it would be expected that',
		options: [
			'The rate of inflation would increase',
			'Wages would fall',
			'Natural rate of unemployment will fall',
			'More than one of the above',
		],
		correctOption: 0,
		points: 20,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which food industry dominates among the agro-based industries in Bihar?',
		options: [
			'Sugarcane industry',
			'Cereal-based industry',
			'Pulses industry',
			'More than one of the above',
		],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 20,
	},
	{
		question: 'In which Indian state is the Flamingo festival celebrated?',
		options: ['Rajasthan', 'Assam', 'Manipur', 'Andhra Pradesh'],
		correctOption: 0,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'The author of world famous Harry Potter series is',
		options: ['Ernest Hemingway', 'Jane Austen', 'J K Rowling', 'Stephen King'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 20,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which Veda depicts the information about the most ancient Vedic age culture?',
		options: ['Yajurveda', 'Rig Veda', 'Atharvaveda', 'Samaveda'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 20,
	},
	{
		question: 'Maginot line exists between which country?',
		options: [
			'Namibia and Angola',
			'USA and Canada',
			'France and Germany',
			'Germany and Poland',
		],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 20,
	},
];
